<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="quotes">
        <item>Calm, be calm!|Karlsson-on-the-roof</item>
        <item>Having reached the end, people laugh at the fears that tormented them in the beginning.|Paulo Coelho</item>
        <item>in order to reach your destination, first of all you should start to walk.|Honore de Balzac</item>
        <item>It\'s kind of fun to do the impossible.|Walt Disney</item>
        <item>Obstacles are those frightful things you see when you take your eyes off your goal.|Henry Ford</item>
        <item>Success is to be in time.|Marina Tsvetaeva</item>
        <item>Take care to get what you like or you will be forced to like what you get.|George Bernard Shaw</item>
        <item>The work that we do willingly, heals the pain|William Shakespeare</item>
        <item>Do what you can, with what you have, where you are.|Theodore Roosevelt</item>
        <item>Always bear in mind that your own resolution to succeed is more important than any other.|Abraham Lincoln</item>
        <item>Who wants - looking for opportunities. Who does not want - looking for reasons.|Socrates</item>
        <item>Love and work are the only worthwhile things in life. Work is a form of love.|Marilyn Monroe</item>
        <item>Inspiration comes only when you work.|Gabriel Marquez</item>
        <item>Let him that would move the world first move himself.|Socrates</item>
        <item>Failure is simply the opportunity to begin again, this time more intelligently.|Henry Ford</item>
        <item>I want it. So it will be.|Henry Ford</item>
        <item>Be yourself; everyone else is already taken.|Oscar Wilde</item>
        <item>I have not failed. I've just found 10,000 ways that won't work.|Thomas A. Edison</item>
        <item>If there is no solution to the problem then don't waste time worrying about it. If there is a solution to the problem then don't waste time worrying about it.|Dalai Lama XIV</item>
        <item>Once in a lifetime, fortune knocks on the door of every person, but at this time a person often sits in the nearest pub and does not hear any knock.|Mark Twain</item>
        <item>Our greatest weakness lies in giving up. The most certain way to succeed is always to try just one more time.|Thomas A. Edison</item>
        <item>Waking up in the morning, ask yourself: \"What should I do?\" In the evening before falling asleep: \"What have I done\".|Pythagoras</item>
        <item>Poor, unfortunate, unhappy and unhealthy is the one who often uses the word \"tomorrow\".|Robert Kiyosaki</item>
        <item>Someone once defined hard work as the accumulation of the easy things you didn't do when you should have.|John C. Maxwell</item>
        <item>Life is like riding a bicycle. To keep your balance, you must keep moving.|Albert Einstein</item>
        <item>Two roads diverged in a wood and I - I took the one less traveled by, and that has made all the difference.|Robert Frost</item>
        <item>I believe that laughing is the best calorie burner. I believe in kissing, kissing a lot. I believe in being strong when everything seems to be going wrong. I believe that happy girls are the prettiest girls. I believe that tomorrow is another day and I believe in miracles.|Audrey Hepburn</item>
        <item>Doubt is a killer. You just have to know who you are and what you stand for.|Jennifer Lopez</item>
        <item>Intelligence is the ability to adapt to change.|Stephen Hawking</item>
        <item>The secret of getting ahead is getting started.|Mark Twain</item>
        <item>Be kind whenever possible. It is always possible.|Dalai Lama</item>
        <item>There is always the possibility that ordinary people will make extraordinary decisions.|Elon Musk</item>
        <item>It is better to keep your mouth closed and let people think you are a fool than to open it and remove all doubt.|Mark Twain</item>
        <item>When everything seems to be going against you, remember that the airplane takes off against the wind, not with it.|Henry Ford</item>
        <item>You can't cross the sea merely by standing and staring at the water.|Rabindranath Tagore</item>
        <item>A day without laughter is a day wasted.|Charlie Chaplin</item>
        <item>Innovation distinguishes between a leader and a follower.|Steve Jobs</item>
        <item>When you arise in the morning, think of what a precious privilege it is to be alive - to breathe, to think, to enjoy, to love.|Marcus Aurelius</item>
        <item>I wake up every morning at nine and grab for the morning paper. Then I look at the obituary page. If my name is not on it, I get up.|Benjamin Franklin</item>
        <item>Smile in the mirror. Do that every morning and you'll start to see a big difference in your life.|Yoko Ono</item>
        <item>I am thankful for all of those who said NO to me. It\’s because of them I\’m doing it myself.|Albert Einstein</item>
        <item>Nothing is impossible, the word itself says \"I\'m possible\"!Audrey Hepburn</item>
        <item>Success consists of going from failure to failure without loss of enthusiasm.|Winston Churchill</item>
        <item>Nothing in the world is ever completely wrong. Even a stopped clock is right twice a day.|Paulo Coelho</item>
        <item>If you are working on something exciting that you really care about, you don\'t have to be pushed. The vision pulls you.|Steve Jobs</item>
        <item>Great minds discuss ideas. Average minds discuss events. Small minds discuss people.|Eleanor Roosevelt</item>
        <item>The starting point of all achievement is desire.|Napoleon Hill</item>
        <item>Do it. Or don't. No need to try.|Master Yoda</item>
        <item>Knowing is not enough; we must apply. Wishing is not enough; we must do.|Johann Wolfgang Von Goethe</item>
        <item>Logic will get you from A to B. Imagination will take you everywhere.|Albert Einstein</item>
        <item>You are never given a wish without also being given the power to make it come true. You may have to work for it, however.|Richard Bach</item>
        <item>The journey of a thousand miles begins with a single step.|Lao Tzu</item>
        <item>An investment in knowledge pays the best interest.|Benjamin Franklin</item>
        <item>Great minds have purposes; others have wishes.|Washington Irving</item>
        <item>Believe you can and you're halfway there.|Theodore Roosevelt</item>
        <item>Jump, and you will find out how to unfold your wings as you fall.|Ray Bradbury</item>
        <item>Genius is one percent inspiration, and ninety-nine percent perspiration.|Thomas Edison</item>
        <item>If you do not think about the future, you cannot have one.|John Galsworthy</item>
        <item>A pessimist sees the difficulty in every opportunity. An optimist sees the opportunity in every difficulty.|Winston Churchill</item>
        <item>The people who are crazy enough to think they can change the world are the ones who do.|Steve Jobs</item>
        <item>Creativity is intelligence having fun.|Albert Einstein</item>
        <item>Life is what happens while you are busy making other plans.|John Lennon</item>
        <item>The best revenge is massive success.|Frank Sinatra</item>
        <item>In the middle of difficulty lies opportunity.|Albert Einstein</item>
        <item>The way to get started is to quit talking and begin doing.|Walt Disney</item>
        <item>May you live all the days of your life.|Jonathan Swift</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>